<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Famous Movies</string>
    <string name="warning_message">There was a problem when requesting information from the internet.\nPlease check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="most_popular">Show Most Popular</string>
    <string name="top_rated">Show Top Rated</string>
    <string name="details_error">There was an error loading the details activity. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="release_date">Release Date</string>
    <string name="vote_average">Vote Average</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="poster_description">Movie Poster</string>
    <string name="error_request_movies_list">Error requesting movies list.</string>
    <string name="most_popular_movies">Most Popular Movies</string>
    <string name="top_rated_movies">Top Rated Movies</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>
    <string name="videos">Videos</string>
    <string name="review_author">By %s:</string>
    <string name="review_text_placeholder" translatable="false">Bacon ipsum dolor amet shankle cow short ribs kielbasa pork belly hamburger kevin pancetta ground round pork loin sirloin rump tenderloin. Salami landjaeger picanha, short loin shankle rump andouille prosciutto ribeye pork chop meatloaf drumstick. Rump meatloaf buffalo salami jowl, porchetta beef ribs tail t-bone meatball ham strip steak pancetta short loin. Ground round drumstick ham jowl burgdoggen bresaola andouille pancetta salami strip steak tail ham hock. Spare ribs flank filet mignon tail, turkey andouille ribeye cupim hamburger pork. Andouille pancetta fatback pork loin, ground round buffalo shank porchetta tenderloin shankle sausage turducken ribeye. Flank cupim pork belly jerky swine hamburger.\n\nDoner jowl flank prosciutto beef, alcatra rump burgdoggen sausage andouille sirloin filet mignon. Filet mignon tenderloin shoulder rump capicola tail pork belly t-bone biltong strip steak landjaeger short ribs hamburger. Shank spare ribs tail beef ribs pancetta. Turducken brisket bresaola swine, short loin tri-tip venison. Doner pastrami frankfurter spare ribs corned beef meatball turkey.</string>
    <string name="no_reviews">There are no reviews to this movie yet.</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="error_message_response">There was a problem receiving information from server.</string>
    <string name="error_message_request">There was a problem requesting information from server.</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
</resources>
